

Phùng Thế Anh Frontend Developer

- 🔁 phungtheanh2001@gmail.com 🔪 0386136374
- O Cau Giay, Ha Noi 5 05/10/2001
- https://phungtheanh.github.io/Portfolio/

PROFILE

I have 3 years experience and many clients are happy with the projects carried out

As a person with good logical thinking and creative ability, I hope to become one of the company's key programmers to bring optimal technology solutions to customers. At the same time, I want to improve my professional qualifications and career capacity

- Active, enthusiastic, honest, careful
- analyze, evaluate, solve problems, find solutions, make decisions, work in groups, communicate well

SKILLS

HTML • CSS • Sass •

Bootstrap • Tailwind •

Wordpress • Javascript •

ElectronJs • ReactJs • Nextjs •

Typescript • Github • RESTful api

ENGLISH

Listen	• • • • •
Speak	• • • • •
Read	• • • • •
Write	• • • • •

EDUCATION

Electric Power University (8/2019 - 5/2024)

Information technology major

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Aneed joint stock company

06/2022 - 01/2024

Frontend Developer

Vietcas Company

04/2024 - present | Ha Noi, Việt Nam

Frontend Developer

Website about courses 🖪

08/2022 - 12/2022

Role: Frontend (Nextjs)

- Cut and complete the website interface according to Figma design
- Combine with BE to combine API for website
- Edit website interface according to customer requirements

Website about global import and export

02/2023 - 06/2023

Role: Frontend (NextJs)

- Cut and complete the website interface according to Figma design
- Combine with BE to combine API for website
- Combine with BA and Tester to edit website according to design
- Edit website interface according to customer requirements

App booking sports - Hisport, Medical record management software - Vietcas EMR, Debt management application - Phieu thu

04/2024 - present

Role: Frontend (ReactJs) and build app with cordova, capacitor

- · Make app functions according to assigned tasks
- Work with BE, QA, BA to complete functions
- Edit, improve, update functions according to customer requirements